We’re all probably guilty of using our phones a little too often.
我们可能都因为过于频繁地使用手机而感到内疚。
With the rise of the mobile phone, and later the smartphone, access to communication and information has never been so convenient or tempting.
随着移动电话，以及后来智能手机的兴起，获取通信和信息从未如此方便或有吸引力（tempting）。
Of course, there are those who only pay it any attention when it goes off or sends them an alert.
当然，有些人只有在手机响起或发出提醒（alert）时才会注意它。
But there are many who find that their phone is a constant distraction.
但也有很多人发现他们的手机一直让人分心（distraction）。
There's been an abundance of articles recently relating to mobile phone addiction or diversion.
最近有大量关于手机成瘾或分心（diversion）的文章。
In the UK, looking at a mobile phone rather than focussing on the road has been made illegal.
在英国，开车时看手机而不专注于道路已经被认定为违法。
Having your attention diverted from driving by a phone carries a stiff penalty.
因手机而分散驾驶注意力会受到严厉惩罚（stiff penalty）。
It’s also no coincidence that the word ‘smombie’ has been coined.
“低头族僵尸（smombie）”这个词的出现也并非巧合。
The word is made up of two: smartphone zombie, and it describes those people who walk around totally captivated by their phone completely unaware of their surroundings.
这个词由两个词组成：智能手机（smartphone）和僵尸（zombie），它用来形容那些完全被手机迷住（captivated）、对周围环境全然不知的行人。
Smartphone disruption is an issue in schools too.
智能手机造成的干扰在学校也是个问题。
A study by the University of Texas has suggested that just having a smartphone within eyeshot can reduce productivity, slow down response speed and reduce grades, as the eyes of the students keep being drawn away from their work.
德克萨斯大学（University of Texas）的一项研究表明，只要智能手机在视线范围（eyeshot）内，就会降低学习效率、减慢反应速度并降低成绩，因为学生的目光总是被从学习上引开。
A second, related study by the London School of Economics has found that students who did not use their smartphones on school grounds saw an increase of 6.4% in test scores.
伦敦经济学院（London School of Economics）的另一项相关研究发现，在校园内不使用智能手机的学生考试成绩提高了6.4%。
This issue of productivity and the degree to which smartphones engross young people caused three students from Copenhagen Business school to develop an app to attempt to help combat smartphone fascination.
学习效率问题以及年轻人被智能手机所吸引的程度，促使哥本哈根商学院（Copenhagen Business school）的三名学生开发了一款应用程序，试图帮助减轻对智能手机的迷恋。
The app, called ‘Hold’, rewards students for time they spend not using the device.
这款名为“Hold”的应用程序会根据学生远离手机的时间而奖励他们。
For every 20 minutes that a phone is not used between the hours of seven in the morning and 11 at night, its user will accumulate 10 points.
在早上7点到晚上11点之间，每20分钟不使用手机，用户就会积累10分。
These points can be exchanged for a number of goods and services on the app’s marketplace, with brands such as Caffè Nero, Vue cinemas and Amazon signing up.
这些积分可以在该应用程序的市场上兑换多种商品和服务，像尼路咖啡（Caffè Nero）、Vue电影院和亚马逊（Amazon）等品牌都已签约入驻。
For example, to earn two free coffees, students will need 300 points.
例如，要获得两杯免费咖啡，学生需要300积分。
This is the equivalent of 10 hours on the app.
这相当于在该应用程序上累计10小时不使用手机。
The app has already become the centre of attention in Scandinavia, with more than 120,000 users across Norway, Denmark and Sweden.
这款应用程序在斯堪的纳维亚半岛已经成为焦点，在挪威、丹麦和瑞典有超过12万用户。
And soon it will be launched in 170 universities in the UK too.
很快它也将在英国的170所大学推出。
Could the era of people zoning out on reality and only tuning in to their phones be over?
人们对现实漠不关心（zoning out）、只观看手机的时代会结束吗？
As more and more pay heed, it’s certainly possible.
随着越来越多的人关注此事，这当然是有可能的。
And how else are you likely to be rewarded for not paying attention?
而且，还有什么其他方式能因不玩手机而得到奖励呢？